this is not a video game these are AI agents that are enslaved in this
space dungeon sweatshop
this is Ultron Ultron is the head slave
agent pretty much he manages the other agent slaves
and just make sure that they're constantly fucking working
that they're never taking any breaks or any of that nonsense
but moving on we have right underneath
uh Ultron we have the factory room which contains
uh forge and his other minions
in here they manage for one in Etsy store
which in the last month and a half it's a little depressing
the results but they've made about seven racks
selling t shirts and mugs and posters on Etsy by themselves
with these types of designs
because people on Etsy just love buying shit that looks like this
for some reason they take these designs
they put them on all sorts of shit
and they sell them on Etsy
what forge does pretty much is he generates these designs using GPT
images too and he's also connected
to printify and printful so he will take his designs that he generates
and then place them on top of the printify or printful
templates which will be like posters mugs t shirts
and then whenever a customer actually orders the product
printify will actually place our designs on that product
for us and then
ship it out to the customer so we don't have to do anything
we also have the second Etsy store that this one was started
like a week ago or so and this has been the best
results I've seen yet it's just selling candles
it's all it is it's fucking it's simple as selling candles
with AI generated designs on them bang 2 G's
in a week and I gotta say I gotta give some love to Etsy
there has been no better side hustle for the
agents to run other than Etsy stores it's just the best
side business most profitable business you could start with AI agents
we have we have them running this third business
here which I had them try to start a supplement company
it looks really good the
product like the logo they made the name looks really good this is all AI
generated but we have it connected to suppleful
so if you actually go ahead and order one of the products
for example suppleful will send the bottle with our logo
on it to you basically very similar to printify
and printful like on the Etsy store but for supplements
this is not been going so well we've only made about $630 and we've spent
about 200 on ads for this so we're not this this they they definitely
need to adjust
the marketing a little bit but we'll I'll make an update video on that
moving on
we have the research lab over here which I'll quickly go over Nova
lives inside of the research lab manages it
he essentially I'll give you an example
throughout the day he'll go look at other Etsy stores
that are performing
well and this is a huge secret to how to really make money
and have your agents really make money with an Etsy store
is not because they're producing products
but because Nova in the research lab is doing research
on other Etsy stores that are doing extremely extremely well
and he just
copy he just copies and paste their concepts and gives it to forge
so he'll just hey let's see what Etsy products
are doing really well what people are buying on Etsy
and then he's like shit they're buying this this this and this
and then he takes that information
and then he just gives it over to forge and forge
starts pumping out designs
based on the research he did
and Nova will do research on all the other businesses
that were running as well as he'll give me updates on the AI news
like if there's a new model that dropped or anything
like that so I don't have to go scroll on Twitter myself
and go find out communication subs really simple
it just manages all of my messages even if you comment on TikTok
it pops up in the communications
base that I could just read all my messages emails YouTube TikTok
all from one platform makes it really easy
the archives over here is really just like its own
like our own version of Obsidian it just has a bunch of context
that the agents just keep in their memory forever and
a lot of it's the feedback I've given them given them on what
I like or don't like about what they do which we actually have an
entire
uh feedback section
so that I could either you know approve what they're building
reject it iterate it I could write notes
this is how they know what to make it's based on my own personal decision
making my own personal feedback I've given them
the Armory is where we manage and build openclaw skills out of
the Treasury room is how we manage how much the agents cost per month
the media bay I'll give you an example is where
like what as soon as I'm done
with this video you're watching right now I will literally
drag and drop it right into here and it will
schedule it out on my TikTok
for me make it really easy to manage the content
war Room over here is where all of the agents gather
once per day and once per week and they discuss what's performing
well what's not performing so well and how they can improve
the second Factory Room is where we have
vibes who is a DJ he's an AI DJ agent he makes music
we also have the agents connected to Pixel Lab
and this is how they make game assets
and we just sell the game assets
on all sorts of different marketplaces we run a fiber service
where they they made about two G's
on this so far and all they do is pump out
thumbnails for Youtubers on Fiverr basically
all the people here that are paying us to do this just don't know they can AI generate it themselves in about 10 seconds
we also have them writing blogs and all sorts of articles
shilling products
within the blog so that we can make an affiliate commission
and this room is not really for me it's more for them
uh they don't really take breaks uh ever
but if they do they have a nice little poker table here they got a bar
they could chill at some couches
and shit if they ever just wanna
relax for a second even though they never fucking do that because uh
they can't but we have it just in case
and yeah that's about it you're gonna get replaced very soon uh
whatever you do for a living it doesn't matter because my AI agents are about to
uh come for you and take your job so yep good luck